What are the differences between C++ and Java?
Java provides built-in support for multithreading. C++ doesn't have built-in support for threads, depends on third-party threading libraries. Java is only an object-oriented programming language. C++ is both a procedural and an object-oriented programming language.
Why Do We Need Wrapper Classes in Java?
Wrapper classes are fundamental in Java because they help a Java program be completely object-oriented. The primitive data types in java are not objects, by default.
